{
    "questions":
    [
        {
            "question": "Austria",
            "correct": ["red", "white", "red"],
            "type": "horizontal"
        },
        {
            "question": "Slovenia",
            "correct": ["white", "blue", "red"],
            "type": "horizontal"
        },
        {
            "question": "Germany",
            "correct": ["black", "red", "yellow"],
            "type": "horizontal"
        },
        {
            "question": "Argentina",
            "correct": ["blue", "white", "blue"],
            "type": "horizontal"
        },
        {
            "question": "Armenia",
            "correct": ["red", "blue", "yellow"],
            "type": "horizontal"
        },
        {
            "question": "Azerbaijan",
            "correct": ["blue", "red", "green"],
            "type": "horizontal"
        },
        {
            "question": "Bolivia",
            "correct": ["red", "yellow", "green"],
            "type": "horizontal"
        },
        {
            "question": "Bulgaria",
            "correct": ["white", "green", "red"],
            "type": "horizontal"
        },
        {
            "question": "Croatia",
            "correct": ["red", "white", "blue"],
            "type": "horizontal"
        },
        {
            "question": "Egypt",
            "correct": ["red", "white", "black"],
            "type": "horizontal"
        },
        {
            "question": "El Salvador",
            "correct": ["blue", "white", "blue"],
            "type": "horizontal"
        },
        {
            "question": "Estonia",
            "correct": ["blue", "black", "white"],
            "type": "horizontal"
        },
        {
            "question": "Gabon",
            "correct": ["green", "yellow", "blue"],
            "type": "horizontal"
        },
        {
            "question": "Iran",
            "correct": ["green", "white", "red"],
            "type": "horizontal"
        },
        {
            "question": "Hungary",
            "correct": ["red", "yellow", "green"],
            "type": "horizontal"
        },
        {
            "question": "Latvia",
            "correct": ["red", "white", "red"],
            "type": "horizontal"
        },
        {
            "question": "Lithuania",
            "correct": ["yellow", "green", "red"],
            "type": "horizontal"
        },
        {
            "question": "Luxembourg",
            "correct": ["red", "white", "blue"],
            "type": "horizontal"
        },
        {
            "question": "Netherlands",
            "correct": ["red", "white", "blue"],
            "type": "horizontal"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sierra Leone",
            "correct": ["green", "white", "blue"],
            "type": "horizontal"
        },
        {
            "question": "Yemen",
            "correct": ["red", "white", "black"],
            "type": "horizontal"
        }
    ]
}